

About

I'm a Credit Risk Analyst with a strong STEM background, thanks to my studies in physics & blockchain technologies and my experience as a fullstack developer. I was also a professional trained cook (also experienced in restaurant reception) as I studied in a Hospitality High School. That allowed me to work abroad while I was teenager, granting me memorables experiences with several people of different cultures.

In my spare time I teach physics and mathematics to High School students as a freelancer.

Education

2022 - 2023 🖪 **ALGORITHMS SPECIALIZATION**

University of California San Diego, US

2022 - 2023 🗔 **DATA SCIENCE SPECIALIZATION**

IBM, New York, United States

2019 - in progress...

BACHELOR OF PHYSICS

Università degli Studi di Milano Bicocca, Milan, Italy

2012 - 2018 **HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA OF HOSPITALITY**

IPSEOA Carlo Porta, Milan, Italy

🕰 Languages

ITALIAN

FRENCH

ENGLISH SPANISH

Contact



<u>Parma, Italy</u>



+39 3770982047



maurizio.falconi47@gmail.com



/MaurizioFalconi

Maurizio Falconi

Credit Risk Analyst

I collected lots of working experiences in hospitality field, therefore i chose to cut it off some from my resume, due to my working goal purposes.

If you are interested to check it out my full working experience, skills and certifications you can visit *falker47/gituhub.io/myresume*

Note: when it appears the icon 🖪 next to an activity you can click on it to see the certification. Every underlined text has its relative link.

Freelance Activity

Q January 2023 - present day

Private STEM Teacher

I'm teaching physics and mathematics to High School students as a freelancer. I'm following **10+ students** with a current average of **25h** of lessons **per week**. You can reach my Teacher Accounts on <u>LeTueLezioni</u> and <u>SuperProf</u> to check my students reviews, or my site that I developed on my own

Working Experience

September 2023 - present day

Crédit Agricole | Via La Spezia 138/A, Parma (PR), Italy

CREDIT RISK ANALYST

I've just started, I'll keep you updated!

February 2023 - June 2023

MasterZ | Corso di Porta Romana 61, 20122 Milan, Italy



BLOCKCHAIN & DIGITAL ASSETS ACADEMY ATTENDEE

Winner of the scholarship for the 5th edition of the training course by AIO Blockchain Lab. The following skills I learned, were put into practice in the development of a final project work, evaluated among the Top 50 of the entire course:

- Blockchain Technologies, Smart Contracts, Digital Assets (CBDC and crypto)
- DeFi, DApps, Centralized and Decentralized Exchanges

March 2023 - April 2023

Blazar Group | Via Besso 27, 6900 Lugano, Switzerland



.NET FULL STACK ACADEMY ATTENDEE

Full-time training course (with project work) where I learned and implemented:

- C#, Azure, MSSQL for backend solutions
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Angular for frontend solutions
- GitHub and Trello for the entire project task management

October 2021 - February 2023

MU Fish | Via Galileo Galilei 5, Nova Milanese (MB), Italy

COMMIS de RANG

Part-time work where I was in charge of:

- · Reception of the restaurant customers
- Booking Management
- Waiting service

November 2017 - January 2022

Da Vittorio srl | Brusaporto (BG), Italy

4th LEVEL CHEF

Job on call in occasion of important events where I was in charge of:

- Execution and Plating of Da Vittorio most famous dishes
- Cooking Line Preparation
- Contact with the Public